### Vaibhav Kumar

Senior System Engineer at Infosys

### Summary

i am working with INFOSYS LIMITED, have 2.7 years of experience in asp.net with C# and telerik control.I did B.TECH from BPUT university with distinction. Apart of that i am well in Asp.net, C sharp, WCF, Wcf Services, Windows Services, Telerik and Kendo UI, JQuery, Java script, Bootstarp.

### Experience

#### Senior System Engineer at Infosys

April 2016 - Present (1 year)

Working as a Senior Software Developer and Handling Deployment, unit Testing and be a part of End to End solution.

#### software engineer at Infosys

February 2014 - April 2016 (2 years 3 months)

As a software engineer involved in project development and coded the application and did unit testing.

#### Languages

**English** 

(Full professional proficiency)

Hindi

(Native or bilingual proficiency)

# Skills & Expertise

c sharp

**C**#

**ASP.NET** 

**Telerik Web Controls** 

**WCF Services** 

**Bootstrap** 

**JSON** 

**Web Services** 

**Windows Services** 

**ASP.NET AJAX** 

**Data Structures** 

 $\mathbf{C}$ 

Java

**JavaScript** 

**Programming** 

**SQL** 

## Education

# National Institute of Science and Technology (NIST), Berhampur

Bachelor's Degree, Computer Science, 2009 - 2013

Grade: 83.50

Activities and Societies: core member of club excell in college vice president of innova club at college

#### ST. JOSEPH'S PUBLIC SCHOLL

High School, science math, 2007 - 2009

Grade: First Division

## Organizations

#### infosys

Senior System Engineer

February 2014 to Present

# Vaibhav Kumar

Senior System Engineer at Infosys



Contact Vaibhav on LinkedIn